好，好，再玩一次，好吗？
All right,let's play one more time,okay?
如果我赢了你就不能去巴黎。
And remember,if I win,you do not move to Paris.
好吧，我就再冒一次险。
Okay. I can't believe I'm risking this again,but you're on.
别忘了规则，乔伊,正面是我赢，反面是你输。
All right,Joe,you remember the rules. Heads,I win. Tails,you lose.
快点扔吧。
Just flip.
-啊，是反面。 -该死的！
- Tails! - Damn it!
嘿，我们为你准备了一个送行会，7点钟开始。
So we thought we'd throw you a little going-away party around 7.
哦，听起来不错嘛。
Oh,that sounds good.
嘿，瑞秋，你明天就要走了，现在还不开始收拾？
Hey,Rach,you're leaving tomorrow. Shouldn't you be packing?
-已经收拾好了。 -哈，是嘛？
- It's all done. - Oh,yeah,right.
今天早上我洗澡的时候，我把毛巾扔在地上了...
And after I took a shower this morning,I just threw my towel on the floor.
-哦，天哪，就算是开玩笑我都心疼。 -我知道。
- Oh,God,it hurts to even joke about it. - I know.
莫妮卡,我是说真的。我全都收拾好了。 要带的行李都在卧室里
Honey,seriously,I did it all. The luggage that I'm taking is in the bedroom.
这些是艾玛要在巴黎用的东西 这些箱子都是要托运的
This is Emma's Paris stuff. These are the boxes that I'm having shipped..
那个是我打算飞机上吃的三明治。
and that's the sandwich I made for the plane.
不过应该多加些芥末
Which could've used a little more mustard.
-看起来你干得还不赖。 -是啊
- Okay,so you've done some good work. - Yeah.
你的手提行李呢？
What about your carryons?
哦，需要的东西全都在这个包里
Oh,well,everything that I need is in here..
而旅行要用到的文件和材料都在台子上。
and my travel documents are on the counter..
我已经把它们按照使用顺序排好了。
organized in the order that I will be needing them.
哦，天啊，我好像没什么要提醒你的了
Oh,my God. I have nothing left to teach you.
-你的护照呢？ -应该跟我的机票在一块。
- Where's your passport? - It should be next to my plane ticket.
-嗯...没有啊? -没有吗？也许我放在这里了？
- Well,it's not. - What? Well,maybe I put it in here?
噢，没有，不在这儿...哦不会吧
Oh,it's not in there!
我肯定是把它封在这些箱子里了...
Oh,no,I must have packed it in one of these boxes!
-我来帮你。 -倒霉...
- Here,let me help you. - Shoot.
真不敢相信...我怎么会放在这儿的...
I can't believe I did this.
玩笑是不是开过头了...
At what point did it stop being funny that I took her passport?
瑞秋的送别会
The.One.With.Rachel's.Going.Away.Party
天哪，只剩三个礼拜了，真是让人难以相信啊。
Oh,wow,can you believe you're only three weeks away?
是啊。
I know.
-你不介意我摸你的肚子吧？ -我不介意你摸我的肚子
- You don't mind me touching your belly? - I don't mind you touching my belly..
但是你的手现在好像 已经摸到孩子出生的地方了。
but your hand's kind of blocking the part where the baby's gonna come out.
- 嘿。 - 嗨。
- Hey! - Hey.
嘿，艾瑞卡,欢迎回来。 哦，你都已经变得这么丰满了！
Hi,Erica. Welcome back to town. Wow,look how big you've gotten.
这是因为我怀孕了！
That's because I'm pregnant.
-哦，对，没错，我知道。 -哦，哈
- Right. No,I understand. - Oh,okay.
我就是怕别人以为我本来就是个胸大的胖妞。
I'm just always afraid that people think I'm just fat with big breasts.
哦，不，不，我不会的。
No,no,I knew.
-嘿，别死盯着人家啊 -是她先提起这事儿来的。
- Okay,well,stop staring at them. - She brought them up.
你怎么这么快就回来了？
I didn't realize you were coming back so soon.
再过两个星期我就不能旅行了。
In a couple weeks I won't be able to travel.
我想让她先见见医生，然后在酒店安顿下来。
And I wanted her to get to know the doctors and get settled into the hotel.
-为什么不让她和你们一起住？-因为我们马上就要搬了
- Why isn't she staying with you guys? - Because we're moving in a couple days.
酒店里很好玩儿啊。我的房间有一个小冰柜塞满了免费的零食
Plus,hotels are fun! My room has this little fridge full of free snacks.
艾瑞卡,那些零食可不是免费的。
Erica,those things aren't free.
实际上，酒店里的食品是最贵...
They have one of the highest markups of any consumer product..
罗斯,她正准备给我们生个孩子 就算她把你吃了都无所谓。
Ross,she's giving us her baby. She can eat you if she wants.
我马上就回来。
I'll be right back.
哎，真不敢相信你们就要离开这儿了。
Oh,man,I can't believe you guys are leaving this place.
是啊...
I know. I know.
如果你想要这间公寓的话可以住进来，仍然是以外婆的名字登记的
You know,you could take it if you want. The lease is still in Nana's name.
哦，不，不。这里永远是属于你们的。 住在这儿太伤感了
No,no. This will always be your place. It would be too sad.
而且... 每个月乔伊会吃掉多少钱？
Plus,how much a month does it cost to feed Joey?
两个人挣的都不够
Yeah,it takes two incomes.
嘿，钱德在么？ 我们约好了要去看电影的。
Is Chandler here? We talked about catching a movie.
他可没那个闲工夫。
Oh,no,he doesn't have time for that.
如果你有空 你可以去客房帮他和乔伊一起收拾东西
You can go help him and Joey pack up the guest room.
嗯...是收拾东西呢？ 还是去看电影里性感的女啦啦队员呢？
Packing. Sexy cheerleader comedy.
嗯...是一个好哥哥呢？ 还是一个去看青春片的老衰人？
Helpful brother. Creepy loner at teen movie.
-你们俩干吗呢？ -快来试试！我一点儿都不疼！！
- What are you guys doing? - Try it. I can't feel a thing.
你们开什么玩笑！
Are you kidding?
-这叫收拾东西么？！ -我们累了，正在休息呢。
- This is packing? - We're taking a break.
怎么会累着的？
From?
...刚才在床上蹦来着...
Jumping on the bed.
好了，瑞秋的送行会就快开始了 我们有一堆儿事情要做呢！
All right,Rachel's party is in a couple of hours,and there's a lot to do.
罗斯,别忘了你流着盖勒家的血 你负责看着这两个家伙！
Ross,you've got Geller blood. You're in charge of these yahoos.
- 知道了。 - 好吧
- You got it. - All right.
她说的对，我们得认真一点儿。
All right,she's right. We gotta get serious.
让我们把这个塞到他的裤裆里，然后踢他！
Let's put Styrofoam peanuts down his pants and kick him!
她说的对 我们得开始工作了 我把柜子里的东西搬出来
No,guys,she's right. We should get to work. I'll take stuff out of the closet.
乔伊你打包， 罗斯你负责把所有乔伊打过的包重打一遍。
Joey,you pack them,and Ross,you repack whatever Joey packs.
你们听到有什么东西嗡嗡叫么？
You guys hear a ringing?
-这是什么鬼玩意儿？ -嘿，手铐，还裹着皮毛！
- What the hell is this? - Hey,handcuffs. And fur-lined. Nice.
真有你们的！不知道你们还来这一手儿...
I didn't know you guys had it in you.
钱德,你没有妹妹 所以你大概
Chandler,you don't have a sister,so you can't understand..
不能体会我现在有多闹心
how much this bums me out.
我不知道莫妮卡什么时候开始有这玩意儿的
I didn't know Monica had these.
嗯，也许这是她用在别的男人身上的。 也许是理查呢...
Maybe she used them with another boyfriend. Maybe Richard.
为什么她和理查玩儿这个，却不跟我玩儿？
Why would she use them with Richard and not me? I can be kinky.
有一次我还光着身子给她跳舞来着 当时我用的是领带。
I once did a naked dance for her with scarves.
越来越过分了...
Bumming hard,guys. Bumming hard.
- 嘿。 - 嗨。麦克呢？
- Hey. - Hey. Where's Mike?
他有一场演出...
Oh,he has a gig.
我越来越觉得自己像是个摇滚歌星的老婆了...
It's kind of like being married to a rock star,you know?
我老公有场演出!
My husband has a gig.
在哪儿演出啊？
Yeah? Where is it?
哦，是一个少儿滑旱冰的聚会。 他去那儿弹琴。
Oh,he's playing organ for a children's roller-skating party.
还真够劲儿啊!
Rock on!
哦，摆了这么大一桌子。这些都是什么啊？
Wow,this is quite a spread. What is all this stuff?
嗯，我觉得今天的晚会是一个好机会。
I thought this would be a great opportunity to use up all the food..
我可以把所有不想带走的食物全都用了...
that I don't want to move to the new house with me.
那么...尽情享受吧。 熏牡蛎卷拌早餐麦片
So enjoy. Smoked oyster casserole with a breakfast-cereal crust.
四季豆加豆浆 然后甜点是...一个过期的橙子。
Kidney beans in their own juices,and for dessert,a questionable orange.
那么,我应该替大伙说话了
Well,I think I speak for everyone when I say:
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
- 嘿，瑞秋呢？ -她在哄艾玛睡觉呢
- Where's Rach? - She's putting Emma down.
马上就过来。 可能是因为要走了，她现在情绪有点激动。
She'll be over in a second. It just hit her that she's leaving.
所以别刺激她，记住了么？
She's kind of emotional,so no one say anything to set her off,okay?
-嘿，瑞秋 -嗨
- Hey,Rach. - Hey.
在这呢
There she is.
嗨，大家好
Hi,you guys.
我刚才怎么交待你们的！！！
What did I just say?
不，不，我没事。
Oh,no,no,no,it's okay. It's okay. I'm gonna be fine.
-过来，我给你弄点喝的。 - 好的
- Come here,I'll make you a drink. - Okay.
哦，天哪，我真不敢相信，她真的要走了。
Oh,man,I can't believe she's actually leaving.
让我怎么开得了口说再见啊
How am I gonna say goodbye to Rachel?
她对我来说这么重要...就好像
I know,she's been such a big part of my life.
就好象梅尔罗斯(美国马萨诸塞州东部一城市) 要被剔除了
It feels like when Melrose Place got cancelled.
我是说..
I mean..
忘了吧,我想念梅尔罗斯
Forget it,I miss Melrose Place.
-我本来有机会阻止她的,- 是吗？
- I had a chance to stop her too. - Yeah?
没想到猜硬币我会连输57次。
Who loses 57 coin tosses in a row? You know?
正面她赢，反面我输嘛...
Heads,she wins. Tails,I lose.
等等...
Wait a minute.
-怎么了，乔伊? -我忘了把衣服从干洗店拿回来了...
- Yes,Joe? - I forgot to pick up my dry cleaning.
你还好吧？
So you doing okay?
嗯，我好多了。你们都会来看我的，对不对?
Well,I've been better. You guys are gonna come visit,right?
当然了！再过6个月我的禁令就过期了。
Yes! You know,in six months,the statute of limitations runs out..
到时候我又可以作国际旅行了。
and I can travel internationally again.
- 我一定会很想你的！ - 我也是。
- I'm gonna miss you so much. - I know.
你知道么，我对你们每个人都有些告别的话要说。
You know what? I have some goodbye stuff that I wanted to say..
我本来打算在结束的时候说的，但是...跟我来。
to each of you. I was gonna save it till the end of the night,but come here.
嘿，你们说她们到屋里去干吗？
Hey,what do you think they're doing in there?
嗯，照我看来
If I had to guess,I'd say..
肯定是瑞秋戴上塑料泡沫， 然后菲比来动手打。
Rachel's putting on the bubble wrap,and Phoebe's doing the punching.
哦，菲比,我真不知道应该怎么开口。
Phoebe,I don't even know where to start.
嗯，这样吧 我知道今天本来不需要给你准备礼物的
Okay,well,before you do,I know we weren't supposed to get you presents..
但我还是准备了一个。
but I do have something for you.
-哦，哦，这是什么？ -是一个棉花棒
- What is it? - Well,it's a cotton swab..
上面沾了些我的口水。
with a bit of my saliva on it..
这样一来 如果你在巴黎的时候发现那边的克隆技术成熟了
so that if they perfect the cloning process while you're over there..
你就可以用这上面的DNA来另外做一个菲比
you can use the DNA to create your own Phoebe.
啊...我可能会把这个扔掉...
I'm gonna throw this away..
但是我很感谢你这份心意...
but thank you so much for the gesture.
钱德？
Chandler?
我刚才在卧室的枕头上发现了这个
I was just in our bedroom,and I found these on my pillow.
哦，我决定把这个先给你留着。 万一哪天理查过来
Oh,yes,I decided to leave those out for you in case Richard stops by..
你可以跟他的胡子一起玩。
and you want to engage in a little light bondage and mustache play.
你说什么呢？这不是我的！
What? These aren't mine.
啊？是吗？
Oh,yeah,right!
以后休想再让我给你跳领带舞了！
Good luck getting another scarf dance from me.
这种“惩罚”太可怕了...
That would be a terrible punishment.
我是说真的。我以前从来没见过这东西。
But I'm serious,I've never seen these before.
真的吗？那它怎么会出现在我们的客房里的？
Really? Then what are they doing in our guest room?
瑞秋曾经在那里住过。
Rachel used to live in that room.
瑞秋...戴着手铐...
Rachel. With handcuffs.
真不错...（幻想）
Interesting.
光着屁股的乔伊（打破幻想）
Joey's bare ass.
真有你的。
Well played.
- 我爱你，菲比! - 我也爱你!
- I love you,Phoebe. - I love you too.
你..
Please..
你可千万...千万...
Please don't..
别...别变成一个...法国婊子...
Don't turn into,you know,a French bitch.
不会的
I won't.
我得继续找其他人了。
All right. Well,if I'm gonna do this,I better keep going.
- 好的 - 好的
- Okay. - Okay.
- 莫妮卡 - 哦！
- Monica? - Yeah?
-跟我进来一下好吗？ - 当然
- Will you come with me for a minute? - Sure.
-你的面霜是防水的么？ - 不是啊
- Are you wearing waterproof mascara? - No.
哦，你完蛋了。
Oh,you're so screwed.
嘿
Hey.
这是怎么回事？
What was that all about?
她打算跟我们每个人单独告别。
She's gonna say goodbye to each of us individually.
哦，开什么玩笑，天哪！
Are you kidding? Oh,my God.
是啊，我知道，轮到你的时候可能会更糟。
Yeah,I know. It's gonna be even worse for you. God.
天哪，准备好好大哭一场吧。
Well,just get ready to do some serious crying.
天哪，我怕我会撑不过去...
Man,I'm not gonna be able to handle this.
我现在终于知道每个学期末我的学生们的感受了。
Now I know how my students feel at the end of each year.
他们因为太舍不得我所以在教师评定中给我打那么低的分数
And why they act out by giving me such bad evaluations.
莫妮卡,好吧
Mon. Okay.
我就直说了。我想说的是...
I better just say what it is I'm gonna say.
如果没有你，我在过去十年里
None of the amazing things that have happened to me in the last 10 years..
我不可能会这么幸福。
would have happened if it wasn't for you.
一直以来，你对我来说就像是姐姐一样。
No one has been more like a sister to me.
我知道
I know what you mean.
我也一直把你当作妹妹。
You're like a sister to me too.
我不知道没有你我会怎么办！
I don't know what I'm going to do without you.
你是我最好的朋友
You're the greatest friend I ever had.
每天都看见你
seeing you every day.
你说什么？
What?
我，我…
I.. I.. I..
每天都看见你
see you every day!
太让我感动了！！！
That is so sweet!
哦，她连莫妮卡都搞定了
Oh,no,she took down Monica.
要知道在盖勒家我是最爱哭的。
And I'm the crier in the family.
哦,天哪，可能该轮到我了。
Oh,God,I could be next.
如果我跟你说话，她可能就不选我了。
Maybe she won't talk to me if it looks like we're deep in conversation.
哦，那么说你之前说的那个什么
Oh,so that thing you said about the thing..
让我想起了那个什么。
it really made me think about that other thing.
- 瑞秋？ -好了，看起来钱德找上她了。
- Rach? - Oh,it's okay,Chandler's talking to her.
你想起了什么啊？
I really made you think about that thing,huh?
瑞秋,我想这个应该是你的吧？
Rach,I think I have something that belongs to you.
你的笑话每次我都得逼着自己乐 我一定会怀念这种感觉
I'm sure gonna miss pretending to laugh at your weird jokes that I don't get.
不，不，这真的是你的。 我们是在你住过的房间里找到的。
No,no,they're really yours. We found them in your old room.
但这不是我的啊 也许这是莫妮卡以前和...
These aren't mine. Maybe Monica used to use them with..
别提理查!
Don't say Richard.
如果这不是莫妮卡的，也不是你的，那是谁的呢？
Well,if they're not Monica's and they're not yours,then whose are they?
我想你大概忘了 在客房里住过的所有人里面，谁是最变态的？
I think you're forgetting the kinkiest former resident of that room.
- 菲比 - 哦 !
- Phoebe! - Yeah!
我想这个是你的吧？
I think these are yours.
这不是我的! 这么松松垮垮的。
These are not mine. Look how flimsy they are. Come on.
如果你用这个把人栓在水管上面
My God,you try to hang a guy from a water pipe with these..
他轻而易举就跑掉了。
they'll snap like a piece of licorice.
- 我能单独跟你谈谈吗？ - 当然。
- Can I talk to you alone for a minute? - Sure.
你不会真的把人拷在水管上吧？
You don't really handcuff guys to water pipes do you?
你以为麦克现在在哪儿？
Where do you think Mike really is?
哦，亲爱的。
Oh,honey..
让我先说两句吧。 要不然待会儿一旦我觉得不自然
Let me just saying something because once we get into this..
我可能又该开始开无聊的玩笑了。
I'm gonna get all uncomfortable and probably make some stupid joke.
我就是想说，我...我爱你。
I just want to say that I.. I love you.
还有就是，我会想你的。
And I'm gonna miss you.
你就这么走了，我真的很难过。
And I'm so sad that you're leaving.
哦，你知道吗
Oh,you know what?
哦，其它的什么也不用说了。
Let's not say anything else.
我也爱你
I love you.
哦，别抱的这么紧！
Not so tight.
- 对不起，再给我一次机会。 - 好吧。
- I'm sorry,give me one more chance. - Okay.
好吧。
Okay.
走吧，走吧。我控制不了自己。
I'm sorry. Just go. Just go. I can't. I can't.
-看来你是下一个了。准备好了没有？ -还没有。
- So I guess you're next. You ready? - I don't think so.
显然你没有。 我几年都没有这么哭过了。
Oh,you're definitely not. I haven't cried like that in years.
昨天晚上你还对着六点钟的新闻哭来着
You cried yesterday at the 6:00 news.
那个老太太被那个修理工骗得好惨！
That old woman was being scammed by her mechanic.
天哪，没想到她居然把我排在最后。
God,I can't believe she saved me for last.
他们俩怎么还没说完？
Why are they taking so long?
不知道 不过看起来乔伊好像没什么事儿，真是意外！
I don't know. But,God,Joey seems to be handling it surprisingly well.
- 不 - 不！乔伊
- No! - No! Joey!
好了， 轮到我了。
Okay,here we go.
- 啊，好吧。 - 嗯。
- Well.. - Yeah.
我想我该走了。
I think I'm gonna take off.
我明天会很忙,所以..
I have such a big,big day tomorrow,so..
- 瑞秋. - 怎么?
- Rach. - Yeah?
你是不是忘了什么事?
Aren't you forgetting something?
- 喔对了. 罗斯 - 怎么?
- Oh,right. Ross. - Yes?
我忘了给你妈妈写生日贺卡了.你能帮我写一张吗?
I forgot to write your mom a birthday card. Would you please do that for me?
- 当然. - 谢谢.
- Sure. - Thank you.
哦大伙,真是奇妙的夜晚啊,非常感谢
Oh,you guys,this was an amazing night. Thank you so much.
我爱你们
I love you.
晚安
Good night.
什么
What?!
都不和我说再见?
I don't get a goodbye?
你这个幸运的混蛋
Lucky bastard.
我简直不敢相信.... 她跟你们每个人告别，却不跟我说。
Unbelievable. She says goodbye to everyone but me!
也许她觉得你们这么多年的默契... 一切都
Well,maybe she thought that with all of your history,it could be..
- “尽在不言中”了呢 - 啊!那起码需要“言”呢
- you know,implicit. - Well,it needs to be "plicit."
你知道,也许她和我们讲话花费不少体力
You know,maybe she was just really spent from our talk.
- 真是非常的激烈啊 - 对啊,我的也是
- It was pretty intense. - Yeah,mine too.
- 我的非同寻常 - 好了
- Mine was a humdinger. - Okay!
我们好好想想，肯定是有什么原因的。
All right,let's think about this. I mean,there's gotta be an explanation.
-你是不是惹她生气了？ -没有啊。
- Did you do anything to make her mad? - No,I don't think so.
那你有没有借她的"野性女孩"录影带 而且又不还
You didn't,say,borrow her Girls Gone Wild video and never return it?
真的?现在?
Really? Now?
我真的那么无足轻重吗？几滴眼泪，一个简单的拥抱...
I mean,don't I deserve anything? I mean,a few tears,a cursory hug?
不是跟你抱！
Not from you!
罗斯,如果你这么在意，你应该去跟她直说。
Ross,if you're this upset,you should go and talk to her.
说什么啊？说“你还没跟我告别呢”？
And say what? You owe me a goodbye?
-他的自尊心往哪儿放？ -什么自尊心，见鬼去吧
- I mean,he's got more pride than that. - The hell I do!
-连再见都不跟我说？ -什么？
- I don't get a goodbye? - What?
你跟别人都告别了除了我？我要做什么你才跟我说句再见？
Everyone gets a goodbye but me? What do I gotta do to get a goodbye?
和你做好朋友？和你约会？
Be best friends with you? Go out with you?
跟你生个孩子？
Have a baby with you?
哦，等一下，等一下，这些我好像都做过！
Oh,wait a minute. Wait a minute! I did all those things!
- 罗斯…-哦，也许我应该体谅你一下。
- Ross.. - Or maybe I'm just not giving you..
也许连续跟五个人说再见是太困难了一点，嗯...
enough credit. I mean,it is difficult to say goodbye to five people.
再见，再见，再见，再见，再...
Goodbye,goodbye,goodbye,goodbye,g..
哦，简直不可能啊！！！
It's physically impossible!
你知道吗，我们这么多年的感情
You know what? After all we've been through..
我真没想到这就是你想要的结局。
I can't believe this is how you want to leave things between us.
祝你在巴黎一切顺利。
Have a good time in Paris.
瑞秋,我知道现在可能不是最佳时机.
Rach,I know this may not be the best time..
但是乔伊又去阳台了,你能过来和他谈谈吗?
but Joey's going over the balcony again. Could you just come talk to him?
-我希望罗斯不会太沮丧。 - 我肯定…
- I hope Ross isn't too upset. - I'm sure he's not more bummed out..
-我比他难过。 -谁说不是呢。
- than I am. - Tell me about it.
看来我们的聚会办得不错！
Well,you can't say we don't know how to throw a party.
我要撤了。
I think I'm gonna head out.
-你打算去哪儿？ -我打算回家睡觉。
- Where do you think you're going? - I thought I was going home to bed..
不过现在我感觉到有人要逼我留下来了。
but I'm sensing there's something less fun for me to do here.
我们马上就要搬家了，有很多东西需要收拾。
We're moving,and we got a lot of packing to do.
-如果你们能来帮忙就太好了。 - 乔伊和我可以继续收拾客房。
- It'd be great if you guys could pitch in. - Joey and I can finish up the guest room.
是啊，是啊，好主意。
Yeah,good idea.
噢，不行。 你和菲比留在这儿帮我。
Oh,no. You and Phoebe are gonna help me in here.
你就不会装得冷静一点。
You couldn't be cool.
好的,让我们从厨房开始。
We're gonna start in the kitchen.
首先盘子放在盘套里，然后十个一组装箱。
Plates get put into plate protectors and stacked 10 to a box.
银器要先用橡胶膜捆上，然后用塑料泡沫包上。 明白了没有？
The silverware gets bundled in rubber bands and then bubble wrapped. Got it?
- 明白了。 -好 ，你们要小心一点
- Yeah. - Good. I need you to be careful..
同时动作要快。记住，如果我朝你们吼叫
and efficient. And remember,if I'm harsh with you..
那肯定是你们哪里做错了。
it is only because you're doing it wrong.
嘿，莫妮卡,我想我知道手铐是谁的了。
Hey,Mon,I think I figured out whose handcuffs they are.
-你怎么知道的？ -我刚才在收拾柜子的时候
- You did? How? - Well,I was cleaning out the closet..
发现了这个…
and I found some pictures of them..
-一些相关的照片。 -天哪，让我看看。
- being used. - Oh,my God,let me see.
那个又老又脏的女人是谁啊？
Who's that dirty old lady?
莫妮卡的祖母。
Monica's grandmother.
哦，天啊 原来她喜欢粗野的！
Oh,my God. Nana liked it rough!
- 嗨 - 嘿
- Hi. - Hey.
- 你们在看什么？ - 哦,只是普通的照片..
- What are you guys looking at? - Oh,just normal pictures..
正常的家庭却没有做爱
of our regular family not having sex.
-来，坐下，坐下。 - 好 .
- Oh,here,have a seat. - Yeah.
-今天晚上过得怎么样？ - 还不错.
- How was your night? - Oh,it was okay.
我和我堂兄去看了场电影 然后一起吃了晚饭。
I went to a movie with my cousin then out for dinner.
我们去的餐厅...
We went to this place that had..
噢...噢... 总之呢，那家餐厅的起司汉堡真是棒极了。
Anyway,they had these really amazing cheeseburgers.
- 艾瑞卡,你是不是不舒服？ -有一点。可能是我吃多了。
- Erica,are you okay? - Yeah,you know,maybe I ate too much.
我的胃一直有点疼，每隔几分钟就疼一下。
I keep getting these stomachaches. They come and go every few minutes.
-哦，天哪。 -别紧张，我们给她点胃药就行了。
- Oh,my God. - Relax,we'll just get her some antacids.
那不是胃痛，那是阵痛的症状
She doesn't have a stomachache! She's in labor!
-哦天哪！ -要赶快送她去医院
- Oh,my God! - Yeah,you gotta get to the hospital!
钱德去拿外套，艾瑞卡我们马上出发。 菲比和乔伊，继续收拾！
Chandler,get the coats! Erica,let's go! Phoebe and Joey,keep packing!
哦，天哪，我们要有孩子了！
Oh,my God,we're gonna have a baby.
We're gonna have a baby!
哦，天哪，我们要有孩子了！
Oh,my God,we're gonna have a baby!
哦，我的上帝，我得坐一下，我得坐一下。
Oh,God,I've gotta sit down! I've gotta sit down!
-亲爱的，一切都会很顺利的。 -你一定能撑过去的，深呼吸。
- Honey,it's gonna be okay. - You can do this. Just breathe.
好好好
Okay. Okay.
我觉得好一点了。
Okay,I feel a little better.
噢...你真的好一点了么？
Are you sure?
-是的，我没事。亲爱的，我们走吧。 - 好
- Yes,I'm sure. Oh,honey,let's go. - Okay.
- 哦，亲爱的，走吧 - 大伙儿再见了！
- Come on,let's go. - Okay,bye,everyone!
- 我们就要有孩子了 - 好运！
- We're having a baby! - Good luck!
- 钱德,等等，等等 - 干吗?
- Chandler,wait,wait,wait! - What?
如果有空的话 帮我问问她那个起司汉堡是在哪儿买的
If you get a second,find out where she got that cheeseburger.
"亲爱的.朱迪
"Dear,Judy.
生日快乐,爱你的瑞秋.."
Happy birthday,love Rach.."
不行,你知道吗?我做不来这个
No. You know what? I'm not doing this.
你真的以为我不跟你告别是因为我不在乎你？
You think I didn't say goodbye to you because I don't care?
看起来就是这样啊
That's what it seemed like.
我真不敢相信，都十年了 你居然对我连最起码的了解都没有。
I cannot believe that after 10 years you do not know one thing about me!
-那你为什么不跟我告别呢？-因为那对我来说太困难了,罗斯
- Then why didn't you say something? - Because it is too damn hard,Ross!
一想到我会那么挂念你 我根本就开不了口
I can't even begin to explain to you how much I am gonna miss you.
每当我想到自己不能再天天看到你 我就不想走了。
When I think about not seeing you every day,it makes me not want to go.
如果你以为我不跟你告别是因为
Okay? So if you think that I didn't say goodbye to you..
你对我来说不如其他人那样重要 那么你错了。
because you don't mean as much to me as everybody else,you're wrong.
对我来说你比他们都重要。
It's because you mean more to me.
好了，现在明白了吧，这就是你要的告别。
So there,all right? There's your goodbye!
- 瑞秋 - 干吗？
- Rach! - What?
-你...你不...你不能... -不能什么？
- You keep.. You can't.. - What?
- 再多塞一点。 -哦。
- A little more. - Okay.
- 再多一点，多一点 - 好
- A little more. A little more. - All right.
再来一点。
Little more.
-行了。来吧。 -好。你准备好了么？
- All right. All right,let's do this. - All right,ready?
好了。记住了要用全力。
Yep. Now give me your best shot.
行。来了
All right. Here goes.
不起作用...
Doesn't work.